syntekoffice.com 2019-05-16

# LivElite -

LivElite International is the parent company behind WoTaBu Adventures, AlureVé, and Syntek.

Ensuring the security of the personal information you submit is a priority of LivElite International. The Privacy Policy was developed to show our commitment to combine quality products and services while also respecting our dealings with our user’s t to protect your privacy and security.

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by LivElite as described in this Privacy Policy.

LivElite adheres to the privacy principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

This privacy policy covers the collection and use of data through the web sites www.liveliteintl.com.

We want your use of the LivElite Site and the services we offer to be productive and safe and we have taken great efforts to keep your information confidential and secure at all times within our system.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us at Support@liveliteintl.com.

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

###  Personal Information 

The LivElite Site collects different types of personal identifiable information (PII) such as name, address, email address and phone number.

In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products, and contact preferences.

Generally, you can visit the LivElite Site without entering any PII. However, if you choose to place an order on the LivElite Site, we require that you provide your name, mailing address, billing address, email address, phone number, credit card number and its expiration date.

All of this information is necessary for us to complete the transaction and update you of your order status.

For distributors, the purpose of the LivElite Site is to manage your distributorship, preferred customers and network of distributors. If you are a distributor, the LivElite Site allows you to order products and manage your distributorship.

Upon creation of distributorship you will setup a backoffice login. This login will allow you to access your backoffice in the future.

When enrolling to become a LivElite distributor and thereby obtain access to www.liveliteintl.com, we collect your PII, including your name, home or business address, telephone numbers, email address, IP address, credit card number and expiration date, bank account information (for direct deposit or direct debit), and various government-issued identifying data, including, but not limited to, your passport number, tax identification number, national ID card number, etc.

This data is necessary to manage your LivElite distributorship for purposes of identifying who you are, placement of your distributorship and of downline distributorships in the tree, compliance management, product ordering, recognition and rewards, and commissions calculations and payment.

We permit your upline to see only the following PII: your name, the country in which you are registered, and your sponsor’s name.

We permit your sponsor to see your name, email address and phone number. We also collect third party personal information from customers, including their name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card number and expiration date. This PII is used to charge for product orders and ship product and for no other purposes.

###  Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, domain type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

###  Testimonials/Product Reviews 

For testimonials, we do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting his or her name and video testimonial. 

If you enter a comment in a public forum we are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these comments.

###  How We Use Your Information 

We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to provide quality customer support or to reach you regarding order status, product or fulfillment issues and other customer service related activities.

We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to contact you regarding new product offerings, special sales, newsletters, market research, and enforcement of the distributor contract and other aspects of your use of the LivElite Site. If, however, you do not wish to receive such communications, you have the ability to "unsubscribe" at any time and you will not be contacted further, unless you place a product order. In that case, we will send you an order confirmation. From time to time, we may ask you to answer surveys regarding current or future LivElite products, as well as to determine hours worked at each rank in the compensation plan. Participation in these surveys is always optional. Survey responses are only used in the aggregate, and are never linked to an individual.

###  Information Sharing and Choice 

LivElite International is not an "information broker. We do not engage in the selling of the profile, contact, web usage habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our customers, partners or users. We use the information we collect about you to process orders, pay commissions and provide the best and most personalized service possible.

We will not use or share the PII provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. We will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will do everything we can to honor such requests.

###  Agents/Service Providers 

We use third parties such as a shipping company to fulfill orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services.

When you purchase a product and use our site, we will share your name, address, telephone number, and email address as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes or any other purpose aside from what is necessary to provide services to us.

###  Business Transition 

In the event LivElite goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred.

You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

###  Legal Disclaimer 

In addition to the circumstances described above, LivElite may disclose or release information when we, in good faith, believe that doing so is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site; (ii) to enforce or apply the terms of distributor agreement; or (iii) to protect the rights, property or safety of LivElite Sites, our users, or others.

###  Links to Other Sites 

This LivElite Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by LivElite.

Please be aware that we, LivElite, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personal information.

**This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this LivElite Site.**

###  Tracking Information 

LivElite does not track users of LivElite Site online activity over time or allow other parties to do this on the LivElite Site.

###  Log Files 

Like most every web site, the LivElite Site records certain tracking information any time someone visits the site.

For every web page that is viewed, our web server records an IP address, the operating system, browser version and the name of the page that was viewed.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses tracking technologies to track non- personal information about visitors to our site.

This information is not linked to any specific user and is used in the aggregate to maintain, track performance and improve the LivElite Sites.

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.

The LivElite Site uses cookies for the sole purpose of uniquely identifying our users and securing their personal information.

We also use cookies to track your order process without requiring reentry or re- verification of password or personal information on each page of the site. Rather than storing this information on LivElite's server, the cookie is stored in your computer and is activated only when you visit the LivElite Site.

Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from the LivElite Site.

No one can access the information except LivElite.

###  Third Party Tracking Technologies 

Some of our business partners use cookies and web beacons on our site. We do not have access or control over these third party trackers.

###  Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs) 

We may employ a software technology called clear gifs (aka Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.

In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personal information.

We may use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.

This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “How We Use Your Information”.

###  Flash Cookies 

LivElite International site does not use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

###  Data Retention 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services and will use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

###  Email & "Unsubscribe" Policy 

We may use your email address provided to contact you regarding the following:

1\. User Registration Status (including confirmation of account signup)

2\. Order Status and Shipping Notification

3\. Online Customer Satisfaction Survey

4\. Major changes to the website, addition of new products or services

5\. Promotional and marketing materials that we think you may find useful

If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest, you can change the notification options in your account settings.

If you wish to not receive any of these emails, you may unsubscribe by emailing to support@liveliteIntl.com or by following the unsubscribe instructions within each email communication.

###  Protecting Your Personal Information 

LivElite is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We place a priority on protecting your Personally Identifiable Information and take commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect such information.

The LivElite Sites use secure sockets layer (SSL) to encrypt the transfer of sensitive information, such as your account password and billing information including credit card, from your web browser to our web server.

Only the last four (4) digits of your credit card number will be displayed in your account. Emails you send to us may not be secure unless otherwise told that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For this reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as credit card numbers or account numbers to us through emails.

The same SSL protocol also acts to authenticate the LivElite Site and prevent unauthorized "Hackers" from pretending as any of our sites while you are logged in to your account. This is accomplished through a "digital certificate", which is an unforgettable electronic "identity card".

If another website attempts to falsely identify itself as a LivElite site, your web browser will display a warning indicating that there is a problem with the digital certificate for the LivElite Site. Do not log in to those sites if you see any such warning.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at Support@liveliteintl.com

###  Updating Your Personal Information 

Preferred customers and distributors can update or correct their personal information at any time by visiting the "My Profile" section of the LivElite Site.

If you wish to access, delete or correct your information, please email us at support@liveliteintl.com or contact us by telephone.

Requests for access will be responded to within 30 days of the request.

###  Children’s Policy 

The Website is not intended for use by children, and children under the age of 18 are not authorized to use the Website and should not submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly market to or solicit information from children under the age of 18.

###  Changes in this Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently.

If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.
